<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>KFGdatafiles</identifier>
  <mediatype>data</mediatype>
  <collection>whirl-archive</collection>
  <creator>Ashok Khosla</creator>
  <description>&lt;div&gt;These xlsx files are data encodings of all legible Andean Khipu 
identified by Ashok Khosla for the Khipu Field Guide. They are an 
important and useful resource to anyone looking to study Khipu and 
Andean communication systems. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All of these files are the product of Ashok Khosla's work for the Khipu Field Guide. It is highly recommended that you visit the site for the Khipu Field Guide as it has many more resources that make the use of these files easier -&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.khipufieldguide.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;https://www.khipufieldguide.com/ &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;All files presented here are protected under MIT License Copyright (c) 2020, 2021, 2022, 2023  Ashok Khosla      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
 a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the 
“Software”), to deal in the Software without restriction, including 
without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, 
distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to 
permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to 
the following conditions:
&lt;p&gt;The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, 
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF 
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. 
IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY 
CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, 
TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE 
SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;                        </description>
  <scanner>Internet Archive HTML5 Uploader 1.7.0</scanner>
  <subject>    andean, andes, khipu, quipu, inca, inka, wari, fiber, writing, numerals, counting, numbers, WHIRLarchive</subject>
  <subject>andes</subject>
  <subject>khipu</subject>
  <subject>quipu</subject>
  <subject>inca</subject>
  <subject>inka</subject>
  <subject>wari</subject>
  <subject>fiber</subject>
  <subject>writing</subject>
  <subject>numerals</subject>
  <subject>counting</subject>
  <subject>numbers</subject>
  <title>Khipu Field Guide - Datafiles</title>
  <uploader>evpaulso@proton.me</uploader>
  <publicdate>2024-08-29 17:46:14</publicdate>
  <addeddate>2024-08-29 17:46:14</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20240829184829[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
  <collection>additional_collections</collection>
  <collection_added>additional_collections</collection_added>
</metadata>
